deliciouslyella.com 2019-05-27

# Privacy Policy - DeliciouslyElla

**PRIVACY POLICY**

At Deliciously Ella, we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

The following Privacy Policy details information on when and why we collect your personal information, how we use it, the limited conditions under which we may disclose it to others and how we keep it secure.

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your Data and how we will treat it.  This covers, but is not limited to, our **Websites** , **Deli** , **Apps** and **Newsletters.   **By using our website, App or other properties you consent to the collection and use of the information you provide to us, as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and without notice, so make sure you check back occasionally.

If we change our Privacy Policy, we will publish those changes on this page. If you have any questions or concerns about our collection, use or disclosure of your personal information, please contact us at [support@deliciouslyella.com](mailto:support@deliciouslyella.com).

Deliciously Ella is the trading name used by The Mae Deli Limited and Deliciously Ella Limited, both companies within the Group ultimately owned and controlled by M&E Mills Holdings Limited whose  Head Office is at: 3rd Floor, 25-26 Poland Street, London W1F 8QN, United Kingdom, and whose registered office is at: 1 Vincent Square, London, SW1P 2PN.

The data controller Deliciously Ella Limited registration reference is: **ZA122304**

### What this privacy policy is all about (in plain English)

We want to give you the best service possible. In order to achieve this, when you interact with us be it in our deli, on our website, within our app or when you subscribe to our newsletter, we will gather information on you in order to improve these interactions.  Some of this data you will formally give us like your email address; other information may be anonymously gathered.

The below summarises how you may interact with us and how we treat your data. Please take time to understand this as it will affect how your data is managed and what you need to do if you have any questions or make any changes.

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify you, such as your name, title, phone number, email address, or postal address.

### Browsing our Website

In general, you can browse the Deliciously Ella website without giving us any personal information. We use several products to analyse traffic to our website in order to understand our visitors’ needs and to continually improve our site for them, such as Google Analytics. We collect only anonymous, aggregate statistics. There are some services on our website that require you to be registered. For example, to receive our newsletter or purchase products from our online store. As part of the registration process, we collect your personal information. We use this information to send you newsletters if you’ve opted-in to receive them, and to fulfil orders from our shop. We will never sell, rent or trade email lists with other companies and businesses for marketing purposes.

#### Use of Cookies

A cookie allows us to analyse traffic patterns to our website. A cookie cannot give us access to your computer or to information beyond what you provide us. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies; consult your browser’s manual or online help if you want information on restricting or disabling the browser’s handling of cookies. If you disable cookies, you can still view the publicly available information on our website. If you are using a shared computer and you have cookies turned on, be sure to log off when you finish.

#### Links to Other Web Sites

Our website contains links to information on other websites, for example, a guest blog post may link to the guest blogger’s website. On websites we do not control, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide while visiting those sites. Those sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and if you have questions about how a site uses your information, you’ll need to check that site’s privacy statement.

### In our Deli

In our Deli, you can log onto our free Wi-Fi.  In doing so, you will be asked to share some personal information with us. The provider of this service is a third party which does hold some Personally Identifiable Information about you when you log onto the free Wi-Fi, such as your email address and location of where you logged in.  This data is held for internal use only, for example we have previously emailed Wi-Fi users an email regarding Deli events (which can be unsubscribed from upon receipt).  This information is not shared with any further parties.

If you have any questions, then please email us at [support@deliciouslyella.com](mailto:support@deliciouslyella.com). We aim to carry out regular checks to ensure the companies we work with and for in respect of holding any data on our customers are GDPR compliant, by reviewing their Privacy Policies ourselves.

### In our Apps

You may download our App’s from the relevant App stores. If you do, please be aware of the below:

#### Free Trial Account iOS

As a Free Trial Subscriber, you can access our app at no cost in the free trial period. In order to access this account, you will need to agree to our terms and conditions along with our privacy policy.

When signing up you may also opt-in to receive our newsletter, but please note if you have not opted in we will still send you emails related to the status of your account, you just won’t receive any marketing emails.

Once this free trial period expires and if you have not cancelled your subscription, your account will revert to a Paid Subscriber Account.

#### Paid Subscriber Account iOS

Thank you for being a paid subscriber! Please note that your actual billing is handled securely through Apple – Deliciously Ella does not hold any of your billing information. As such if you have any billing enquires you need to contact Apple on this address: contact@apple.com.

Please note you will need to contact Apple separately for the information they store on you such as billing.

#### Legacy Apps

We are always improving the apps we have, and you may have previously downloaded apps that are no longer live in the app store to download. These apps will not be updated and will likely encounter compatibility issues on certain devices and may contain out-of-date information.  We will not actively gather any information from these apps but still retain the ability to monitor anonymous activity.

### Social Media and other platforms

We use social media and other similar platforms such as Instagram or Facebook to interact with our customers. When this happens you will have a direct relationship with these platforms and agree to their terms of use. We only have information that you have agreed for us to access through these platforms. We are not responsible for these platforms and how they manage your data. Should you have any privacy related questions please contact them. If you have any questions about our social media activity please contact us at [support@deliciouslyella.com](mailto:support@deliciouslyella.com). ** **

### Newsletters, Competitions & Marketing Preferences

You can subscribe to our newsletters and marketing materials though our apps, websites and other channels and this includes entering competitions through, or subscribing (opting-in) to in to receive information from us through other channels.

You can always unsubscribe to our newsletter or marketing materials at any time, by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our newsletter emails or by emailing [support@deliciouslyella.com](mailto:support@deliciouslyella.com).

### Access to Your Personal Information

You are entitled to access the personal information that we hold on you. Please email your request to [support@deliciouslyella.com](mailto:support@deliciouslyella.com). You can also ask us to remove any of the personally identifiable data we hold on you under ‘right to be forgotten’ regulations so long as this does not affect the services you may be subscribed to.

### Disclosure of your data

To provide our services to you, we may share your Data with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries from time to time, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may also share your Data with third-party service providers who provide IT, sales, marketing and system administration services.

We may aggregate and anonymise your Data and share with selected third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions;

In rare cases we may disclose your personal information:

  * in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;
  * if Deliciously Ella or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets;
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or
  * to protect the rights, property, or safety of Deliciously Ella, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Where we store your personal data

Some Data that we collect from you may be stored and processed outside the EEA by our service providers based in the USA who provide IT, sales, marketing and system administration services (all of whom are Privacy Shield certified). Please contact us if you would like further details. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All Data you provide to us is stored on secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access Deliciously Ella, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. You must not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your Data transmitted to Deliciously Ella; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

### How long we keep personal data

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. We will delete your personal within 30 days if you delete your account.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

### Your Rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will inform you (before collecting your Data) and obtain your consent if we intend to use your Data for such purposes (unless in respect of our own marketing if you are an existing customer and have not opted-out of such communications) or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at support@DeliciouslyElla.com or clicking on “Unsubscribe” when we send you any electronic marketing.

Deliciously Ella may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. You also have the right to access and receive a copy of information held about you, to request the erasure or correction of your information, to object to the processing of your information or to restrict such processing, and to request the transfer of your data. Where we rely on your consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time.

You have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach the ICO so please contact us in the first instance.

### Changes to our privacy policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy at any time and in the event of such a revision, you may be asked to read and accept the revised policy at the time you start Deliciously Ella.

### Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to  [support@deliciouslyella.com](mailto:support@deliciouslyella.com)
